Oh sick. Okay, and I have.
2 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
I have like eight questions, so I am probably gonna just I'll just start with those or maybe maybe I'll let you start. Do you have anything off the top of your head working with other stakeholders and partners that you find are key or critical to your success or things that you have to do, things that you do differently when you're doing that activity?
3 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Yeah, I, I do. There are things that I've tried to ingrain in how I talk to people, what do I talk to them about? What's the engagement like, that I.
4 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
I try to keep at the forefront. I I try to make the priority, but it's never, I I try really hard to not make it about my success, but more about the success of the interaction, the collaboration or whatever.
5 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Whatever I'm proposing or the reason behind why I'm reaching out, right? And so, from a VDS perspective, a lot of conversations I have are about what is VDS and why I think, teams need to be leveraging it within their space. Obviously there's some, well, mostly self serve.
6 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Service around like it's in my best interest, it's one of my top KPIs that I increase adoption of the system. But ultimately I truly believe that teams get gain benefit and value out of it. It is a, a forced multiplier, and so any time that I'm having conversations with someone around video.
7 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Yes, it's important to me to make sure that I'm focusing on their outcome, not mine. Because at the end of the day, if VDS is not of value or helping this person out, I need to be open to that, aware of that, I need to be understanding of that and not push the issue.
8 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
But when I say don't push the issue like I need to make sure I understand what the potential detraction de detraction is with using VDS, what the cons are, and then understanding whether or not that's something that we can improve within VDS or it's just like, well, NO, that's competing priorities. I understand this probably isn't the best. Thanks for having the conversation and being able to, to walk away, right? But if I were to distill that out, I mean it's empathy, right? Understanding and empathizing with whom I.
9 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
I'm speaking with, making sure I understand what's important to Kevin, what's important to Kevin or what, what KPIs or goals does Kevin have? And do I honestly think VDS or whatever is of value or of interest to Kevin? And then just trying to position it in that way? 2nd thing is that that was all one big.
10 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
Thing. 2nd thing I would be.
11 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
I would I focus on is the engagement should not all be around, it should not be all transactional, right? And so, even though I might want Kevin to utilize VDS and the conversation is around VDS and Kevin's usage of VDS, I also want to know about Kevin. Hey, what, what are you doing? Like, what kind of things do you find interesting in your work? What do you like working, what do you like about working here? Why haven't we cross paths and, and.
12 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Like more opportunities, right? And just being personable and saying, you know what, even if you don't use VDS, we can still be friends, we can still be colleagues and have a warm relationship and that requires investment with people in general, and wanting to be invested in other people's lives. Again, whether they do or do not use VDS, right? And so that's, I try to focus on those two things, like building the relationship and then understanding enough about the person and the team to know.
13 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Whether or not what I'm pitching is actually a value.
14 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
Well, those are awesome, awesome, awesome points. How do you try to build rapport and trust? I think you just maybe answered that with new partners or teams, but.
15 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
1II can't be shy about reaching out to people. I like to define myself as an extroverted introvert, right? I.
16 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
It's it's something that has been a grind, an uphill battle for the last 15 years of my career is knowing that the relationships that I build, are much more important than the services or value that a, a pro.
17 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Product or tool that I have is gonna serve, right? And so I need to build connections and build relationships if I want to be successful, but then also you know if I want people like me, if I wanna like my job and like the environments that I'm in, if I wanna be a part of building a culture here that I would want to be in, like I have to invest with that and or invest invest.
18 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
In that. And so in order to build trust and and rapport, I, I gotta make sure that every interaction I have with someone is not transactional, which is why with in each conversation that needs to have a transactional element in it, I try to also build in some of the relational like conversation communication, but then if there's any ever at any time an opportunity.
19 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Opportunity for me to reach out to someone and have a conversation has NO transactional element at all to it. Like I try to lean into that because I think that that has been the biggest I guess four forced multiplier in building relationships at Verizon is just connecting with people even when you don't need anything from in return. Bonus points, if it's just to reach out and say, hey, is there anything I can do for you? Like I'm working on something, I don't, I don't care if it, if it works for you, but is there anything I can add to this that.
20 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
That might help you in the future, right? And those types of things, has, I, I think had a huge impact on my ability to build trust across organizations especially within GTS. Cause that, that was a rocky start.
21 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
And, and one that.
22 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Were required a lot of time and investment, not even before I joined the design organization, to build that relationship up with mutual trust and vulnerability.
23 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
You know that you see I I didn't think of this before, but you are the person we could talk to about that when it gets to that point, and I'm sure you know this is a, this is a conversation I feel like we've I've had for the last eight years that I've been here about, hey, what's our relationship with development or GTS and, you know, how, how can we build that and like I'll be honest that it hasn't really developed. I feel like since I've been here, and you just, sorry now we're going on with a tangent, but I just realized you are someone that has developed that because you had to, because you have the system and they have to use it and there has to be that.
24 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Quite frankly, Kevin, I think my my pre existing relationship with GTS was one of the determining factors that got me the, that really a top candidate for the design system role. Okay.
25 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Because I was I was doing this very similar work in digital, within Diesa Cardi's group before Dye was there Bill like working with a development team that did not sit in GTS and partnering with GTS to co develop co program code, deploy.
26 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Co triage like just being in the foxholes and the trenches with them through hundreds of releases and. Deployments and crisis bridges and understanding the workflow process, why, what they're concerned about.
27 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Why, like understanding their hesitancy around a lot of things is all gonna come back to stability of the underlying systems, the complexity of the underlying systems, very few people understand it. Even fewer people care about it and they're just like just deploy something. Like I don't I don't.
28 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
And so again empathy in that played a huge part. Like, I understand like this is this is shaky, but this is what I'm trying to do. Can you work with me to find the best way to achieve both, right? And I, that, that did a lot in those early years and then I was able to like.
29 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Demonstrate that and express articulate that successfully to Richard, and he saw that as a Boon with my experience, especially going into like how can we increase the adoption of VDS with our GTS partners? And I like to think I've been somewhat successful in that since being in that role, but that.
30 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
That wasn't something I built once in this role. That was something I brought in with me and I've continued to nurture and cultivate it.
31 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
That's interesting though but same kind of principles, empathy, understanding what motivates them and what's what's important to them and how you can help. Yeah.
32 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
It's it's surprising the number of people who think that when you're working with another team and they push back, that it's solely out of animosity to you. Like.
33 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
There's NO reason for them to push back. They just hate me. That's why, so I just have to be more aggressive and push it through. Well, NO, if they're pushing back, there's likely a good underlying reason for that, that we don't understand, and if we understood it, then it creates a better space to have dialogue on how to collectively work around those issues and still be able to achieve the goal.
34 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
So I feel like this goes into a topic. What are the pitfalls you've observed that can hinder effective cross team partnerships? I think you just said one, which I think is interesting. So rather than animosity, it's a lack of understanding or an opportunity.
35 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Hey I guess. Yeah, I a lack of understanding but also which this might go hand in hand with it. It's just having a narrow mindedness or a narrow view of what's at play, where, you know what's interesting I used to be on the other side of the table. Like, I I used to work for a development team that actually built out the designs that came out of CMO. So like Roberto's team before Roberto earned it or owned it.
36 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
We would get designs from them and we would have to build them out and deploy them to the site. And there is a stigma around, you know, design doesn't care about what happens after design. Like they're gonna do their design things and then throw it over the the wall and then if it doesn't go flawlessly, then everyone is gonna get thrown under the bus by design.
37 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Like that was the view and, you know, like accurate or not, that's not the point. Like that view existed or persisted, you know, five years ago when I was in that organization and so like I, I was able to play that to my advantage when working with GTS and was just like, Yeah GTS, they don't even get us. They don't know.
38 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
What we're trying to do here. So it's kind of like the common enemy thing, but then coming over design, I was able to flip that back and be like, I I totally get it. I understand the perception. Let me see what I can do to kind of clear this up and provide more transparency and visibility into the process so that I can get you and we can all work in a more cohesive way. And so, your question was some of the.
39 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
You gotta be open to the downstream, like there are so many issues, hurdles, obstacles that those teams work through on any given day and knowing the the hurdles we go through on the design side, getting stuff last minute, executive escalations, don't work on that, work on this, and it's gotta be out tomorrow. They're doing like everyone.
40 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
The downstream of us is dealing with the same thing except they're looking at us as the one as the ones initiating it where we're looking at leadership as the ones who are initiating it. And like have just having that broader understanding of reality's relative, what's their reality look like? And then being like, ok, I mean that's, that's just like my reality, just like shifted blame like let's see how we can work through this together. Not doing that is the pitfall. Great.
41 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
So I assume you have to stop at all twel.
42 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Well I can go a little over I can give you the time back then.
43 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
Okay, yeah, I mean, whichever but this is this is great. I think you answered this before, but how do you ensure that the collaborations are mutually beneficial and all stakeholders feel like their perspectives are valued?
44 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
I will I can't ensure it. I try, I try to maximize that outcome and more so, well, I try to maximize the outcome by like making sure I'm not just giving lip service, to understanding what my collaborators.
45 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Outcomes are, but they're, that they're trying to achieve. Like, ok, I'm trying to do this. Kevin, you're trying to do that. I understand that. Now, let me put your thing over to the side, let's work towards my thing. But it's constantly coming back and saying, are you still finding that your needs are being met? Are there things that we might be overlooking?
46 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
On that are important to you, if we've, if I feel like we've been focusing too much on my priorities, like always trying to come back and normalize, like making sure all stakeholders in a project are being heard, their concerns are being validated and elevated and cared for.
47 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
And just trying to rebalance, as frequently as as makes sense, which reinforces the idea that this is important to me, which it is, but like you had, that's not not something you have in one conversation and then you check a box. You have to constantly.
48 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Reaffirm, like it's important to me that we both succeed in this. And so what are the things that we can do to ensure that together? And that's not something that I I've seen teams proactively bring up or bring up multiple times throughout the course of a project. So I'm like, well, ok, then I can be that voice and and.
49 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
I'll ask those questions and make sure other teams are, being supported. Here, here's a good example like especially in my previous role before coming to the design system team, I was on a lot of late night calls, like release bridges.
50 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Crisis bridges, all sorts of bridges where I was vouching for my team, I was communicating from my team, raising our own concerns, what we needed, but there were a lot of GTS partners who we were working with, like the, the frontline GTS workers who were.
51 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
We're actually building the experiences and deploying their leadership might not be there or even design in certain circumstances or are seen seven image partners which ironically is under me now in this role. They did not have always have leadership on representing their needs and concerns. And given the audience on the bridges, they might not feel comfortable speaking up for themselves in certain environments and I tried to be super su.
52 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
And aware of that and speak up for them on their behalf, if I knew that they weren't being cared for, if I knew that they had concerns that weren't being communicated, then I would, I would step in and do that. I tried to do that on the VDS side as well as much as it makes sense, but, yeah, like.
53 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
There's probably a more succinct way to explain or describe that, but like caring not just for my team, but for other teams who might not have their leader present to care for them is also a way to ensure.
54 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Mutual success, but it also helps build trust and rapport as well being an advocate that that's it. Being an advocate for not just your team, but for doing the right thing and making sure all things that need visibility are, are getting that visibility.
55 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
That is wonderful. Love it. This is a tricky one I feel like but I don't I wouldn't have a good answer for this necessarily. How do you stay informed about the priorities and challenges of your partner teams?
56 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
That well that that is a tricky one. I ask, I listen, I take a lot of screenshots whenever things fly through a presentation. I'm like, I've never seen that before. Make sure I have my high keyed screenshot taker and then I ask questions.
57 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
One thing I I have had to work at over the years that I think I'm really, I'm much, much, much better at now is, seeing things that are surprising to me and it elicits an emotional response, like.
58 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Oh my god, how could you keep this from me here? Why why why are you trying to make this a secret or why isn't this more power? Again, thinking like the, the reason I don't know about this is because you've been actively trying to keep it a secret from me and then responding under that assumption, 99 % of the time has always been an incorrect assumption.
59 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Right, and it's just been a misunderstanding or like NO it has been circulated, I just didn't see it or I had it and I just didn't look at it. And so being exposed to something after I thought of I should have been, I always just express gratitude. Oh, well, thanks for sharing this with me, like let me review it and understand it more. And then I like asked myself.
60 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Questions on the side in my head, like, ok, let me let me assume the best of people and that there's likely something I missed, something, I I did not look at, and even, even so, does it even matter? I have it now. What's the best next best thing.
61 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
What I can do with this information now. In terms of understanding like proactively going after priorities, that is one of the main 1st things I talk about when I meet people for the 1st time. So, for instance, like we're trying to drive adoption of VDS within the TBD teams. So within the.
62 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
R one apps, family home protects. They don't use VDS a lot. I just learned about this team early last year, and so, you know, the most aggressive myopic approach would have been, I just go to them and say, hey, I have this awesome thing. You need to, you need to utilize it. Like full stop, that's the end of the conversation. But on the other end of that instead.
63 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
And this is more addictive of, of my natural way of going and talking to people. It's, hey, my understanding is that you're doing this, I do this over here and I have this tool, I think it's really cool that potentially could be of use to you, but I honestly, I just wanted to learn more about you.
64 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
What do you, what does your team do? What are your goals? What's important to you? What are you trying to do this year? And I just thought it'd be great to get to know you, right? And just learn that way. And then if it makes if it makes sense or if I see opportunities to say, oh, that's a really cool goal you have, I think my.
65 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
That tool can actually help you enable that faster, then, then I can pitch it that way, right? But again, that's like a secondary objective. The primary objective is just to learn and understand, meet someone new. And the worst case honestly, the worst case is I made a new friend and I know more about the organization.
66 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
Ryan.
67 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
So that's, that's how I try to learn, learn about priorities in my peers. The 1st part of that was how do I respond when I find out late about things? But I do try to be proactive in asking about what's important to you, and then I reciprocate by saying, well, hey cool, this is why I'm doing, this is what's important to me. Maybe some of our things overlap with each other and we can help each other achieve these things faster.
68 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
That's awesome. So I think we have, what, 78 min, something like.
69 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Yeah. Okay.
70 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
From your perspective, what, what does it look? What are the hallmarks of a truly affective partner? What does that look like to you?
71 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
I honestly, so I I've been talking through the things I value and how I go into conversations. I look for those things in other people too. Like, do I only talk to this person when they need something from me?
72 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Are they only open to ideas that they present? They're not ever open to mind. Do they have any idea what I do or what's important to me? Like, I asked those questions. If I'm not in the room, like do they vouch for me or the needs of my team if things come up, if given the opportunity, and so.
73 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Okay.
74 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Yeah, like depending on the answers to all those questions would determine whether or not I, I think you're a good partner or not. Now that doesn't mean I won't partner with you as best I can, right? But in terms of gauging, oh yeah, this is a mutually beneficial relationship or nope, I gotta work, this is all one.
75 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Inside I have to work much harder, and so, you know, if it if if the the relationship is not mutual or it's not beneficial enough for me, then there's NO point in me expanding so much energy into trying to maintain it. Some some people are just like that. And so I don't want to waste my energy in those areas when it's better served building collaborative partnerships elsewhere.
76 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
True true. How about, can you think of any like subtle but powerful ways that you can build credibility and trust with stakeholders?
77 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
So.
78 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
Yeah. Yeah, I.
79 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Making the conversation about the.
80 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Anytime you talk to him, make the conversation about them. Like they're, they're almost always going to be openings for you to like.
81 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Pitch your idea or get your questions answered. But again, like if you make that the secondary objective and the primary objective is just learning more about the other person and and taking a genuine interest in them, like that's, that is so low key and subtle that people just don't ever think about it.
82 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
Awesome. And then I think this could be my last one. If you have like one piece of advice you would give to someone looking to improve their cross team, influencing and partnership scale.
83 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
Else.
84 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
I'm sorry how many things was it the top thing or like a top?
85 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
Oh, you can give me, I would say a top thing and if you have additional things i'll.
86 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Well, I mean I'll probably just mash all of this up and.
87 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
Sure.
88 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Cramble. One thing that I've done, and so this is obviously what I would advise to other people or or give advice, hey, you should be doing this too. When I, got this role of senior director, actually, NO, you know what? Let me let me take a step back. If this is your last question, I I can.
89 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Unload on this. There were some a few things that I think were critical to my ability to move from senior manager to director or associate director to senior director. However we.
90 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
Want to frame that.
91 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Because it was senior manager to director when I, when I made this shift. It was, I got some, well, 1st I had a mentor who was a director, who talked to me about when I was able to talk to them about what I wanted out of my career, what I wanted out of my own personal growth, and I was able to get feedback from them on.
92 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Like, what's that delta look like? I had my perspective on what the delta looked like, but I got their perspective on what the delta looked like. And they were able to, to coach me on a number of things. One of the things that this person shared with me.
93 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Was about, your ability, well one, go moving from a band six to a band five is a complete shift in or at least it should be, a complete shift in, the type of work you're doing where band six and below you're really creating things, you're working down, you're.
94 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Working with your team, you're working with other people at your level. At the band five level, it's really just all about communication and storytelling. Like you need to motivate teams. You need to motivate not just your team. You need to motivate other teams to work with you as well. You need to pitch ideas and and storytell not only to your peers but to your vice president and other VPs and even svps, like you're gonna have to storytell up.
95 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
And so, one of the key drivers of that is who knows of you? Like, does anyone know you outside of your team? And so that was one of the 1st kind of, reality checks I had, like, well, how.
96 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
How out and about am I? Like how often do I get out and talk to people outside of my circle? Do people know me outside of my team outside of my organization across other organizations? How well do they know me? What do they think about me when I work with them?
97 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
So that was, that was the 1st thing. And 2nd thing on top of that was, do I have people who vouch for me, right? Who are at a higher level and speak favorably about me when I'm not there in the room? And so I'm I'm saying all this because it's like, well.
98 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
If those are the outcomes I want, what do I need to do in order to, give myself the best chance for success to have those outcomes? And so I had to be way more extroverted than I was comfortable with. And again, over time you build up confidence, you build up comfort. Although I'd still would love to not talk to anyone during the day.
99 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Like that's my job.
100 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
Like I gotta get funny you say that cause I I think I am also an introvert transformed a little bit into an extrovert. Although for me the key question that said maybe I am an extrovert is does it energize you talking to people? And I realized the answer for me is yes.
101 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
There you go, but I enjoy it, but anyway, sorry. Yeah, so I mean.
102 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
So th that was when I applied for this role, my director at the time reached out to Richard and said, hey, you have a candidate who just applied from my team. I think he's the best person for this role that you're gonna find. My mentor actually reached out to Richard's Jeff Walls, our SVP at the time, had reached out to Jeff Walls and said, hey, there's this person applying for this role, I think.
103 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
It's the best person you're gonna find. And so I had several people writing letters of recommendation that I I did not even anticipate. My director actually reached out to Sasha Sasha Lucas, who was my VP at the time, and Sasha wrote Jeff Walls a letter of recommendation for me coming over as well, which I did not.
104 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Participate at all, but I'm not, this isn't a brag, but it's just like all of those things would not have been possible if I weren't trying to present my best self to people and I was trying like intentionally trying to.
105 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Network, across not only my organization but other organizations, and not just to get work done, but just to be a good person and build relationships, build the culture, right? So that I think that was a huge enabler for me, being considered for the role.
106 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Again, my relationship with GTS was one of the determining factors I think in landing the role. But when I started as a director, the 1st thing I did was especially moving from outside the CMO or the design organization into the design organization, I didn't know a lot of people. So like.
107 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Who are my peers? Like Brandy, Alexa, Brian. I was in Arkansas too. Yeah. Yeah. And so I'm like, I need to get to know all these people. Like I intentionally like set out to have time on the calendar, get to know them, meet them. I also.
108 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
I had standing calls with Richard Weekly, like I've had weekly calls with Richard since I started, which is, is great. Like that normally doesn't happen. And so like I'm like, how can I take advantage of this time with him? I made a list of all the VPs in the company.
109 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
And, and I said, how many of these people do I know? How many of these people do I cross paths with? Cross paths with, how many of these people does my the VDS impact? Like, does it make sense for me to call call and say, hey.
110 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
We're working together in this space. I just wanted to reach out and get to know you versus, hey, we don't even cross paths, but I just wanted to reach out and say, hey, let me know if there's anything I can do for you. And so I I definitely had a hit list of people that I thought would be in my best interest to, to know, get to know.
111 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
And then try to artificially create scenarios where I can get in front of them and start building relationships. So that is what I would propose people to do. You, you have to be more open to having conversations more often. You have to network even for the sake of networking, even if it's not any value to you, if you can give value to them, it's worth it. And then.
112 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Be intentional with it, right? Who are the people like ideally, you would want vouching for you some day and then how can you go about creating a relationship with those people? Now, obviously you can't do that with everyone. Some people are just like leave me alone. I don't I don't want to know you. I did run into.
113 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
Some of those people and I'm sure you did. That's fair. But that, that's the my.
114 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
I would say about, 10 % of the people are just like, I'm fine if we don't ever talk again. Then there's another 40 % of people who are just like me neutral. If you reach out to me, great, I'll talk to you. If you don't fine, I won't talk to you again. But I would say an overwhelming majority.
115 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
50 it's 50 % is not an overwhelming majority. The other 50 % would be, are very personable, they're doing the trying to do the same thing, trying to build connections, trying to look for mutual value, and they might just not have a connection to you, right? And so you reaching out and making connection to them is mutually beneficial, so.
116 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
The the intentionality behind it is I think really big. That is awesome.
117 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
Well, I think we are over our time and I, I really appreciate your time and for making time and again I think I said this in slack, but it was it was great working with your team. I do actually miss working with them on a more regular basis and whatever you're doing it obviously is working because they're, they're very what's the word I wanna look for? Just one last thing. I I was thinking about this the other day, I was thinking about.
118 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
My real our relationship team's relationship with VDS versus maybe you could say a similar team like maybe brand or creative integrated IMC and I'll be like, so there are similar situations aren't they?
119 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
In a way, right? Like once one's one is kind of has a system or structure that is supposed to be beneficial to me I'm supposed to follow, and yet it's quite different the relationship and with your team, I always felt like we were trying to mutually achieve something they would work with us, they were like, well, there's a reason we.
120 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
Don't wanna do this, and then when they explained it, it always made sense, you know, it always made sense to me from a systematic standpoint and I got it I was like, ok, and it wasn't like I felt like you're just telling me you don't want to do it because you don't want to do it for whatever reason. So that was very, I mean I just I wanna pass that back to you. I was really thinking about why was why did that, why does that work so well? And I I valued and kind of missed that relationship.
121 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
And on this other one that's similar, you know, we didn't have the same sort of relationship that I would have liked, but anyway, so just, just appreciate that so I appreciate you sharing that. Thank you. Yeah, yeah. Take care, have a great Thursday and have a great weekend.
122 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
You as well, let me know if there's anything I can do to help support.
123 "Kevin Trayner" (1869335808)
Thank you.
124 "Andrew Pendleton" (2477978880)
Thank you. Alright, see you Kevin. Bye.